Breaking news this evening, Jasmine Crockett is defending Jeffrey Epstein to defend one of her associates.
Watch.
Stacey didn't initiate that chain.
Jeffrey initiated that chain, and she took the information, just like if somebody texts me.
Yeah, but she was responding and saying, you know, what are you talking about quick?
I'm up next.
And then her questions were about Rona.
But do you think that was inappropriate?
I mean, would you text someone who is a registered sex offender about what you should ask?
I honestly know that he had never been convicted of any federal crimes at that time.
But he had been in jail already.
He had been in jail.
And my deal is this.
The Republicans are constantly texting with a 34 count convicted felon.
That lady is trash.
Any of y'all defending that lady is trash.
And I regret ever giving her the time of day.
Good night.
Support a real one.